{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076000123","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076000123"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076001307","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076001307"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" NINAPOMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076001901","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076001901"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076002135","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076002135"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076002579","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076002579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076003284","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076003283"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076004218","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076004218"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076006611","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076006611"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076007135","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076007135"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076008178","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076008178"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076008786","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076008785"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076009410","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076009410"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076010452","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076010452"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076012937","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076012937"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076013816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076013816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076014281","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076014281"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076015284","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076015284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076017723","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076017723"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076018708","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076018708"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076021923","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076021922"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076022417","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076022417"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076022526","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076022526"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076023245","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076023244"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076024222","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076024221"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076024909","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076024907"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076025740","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076025740"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076026328","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076026327"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076028761","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076028761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076029223","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076029223"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076029697","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076029696"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076030482","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076030481"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076031057","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076031056"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076031746","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076031746"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076032353","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076032352"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANYWA"," userResponse":" KUYANYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076034900","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076034899"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076035788","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076035787"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076036259","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076036259"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076037274","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076037274"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076039797","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076039797"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076040792","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076040791"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076044330","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076044329"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPAZIA"," userResponse":" MAPAZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076044408","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076044408"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076045371","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076045371"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADIRISHA"," userResponse":" MADIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076047085","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076047085"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" YANAPAPATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076047689","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076047689"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076048133","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076048133"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076048677","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076048677"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076050377","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076050377"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANANIPANGUSA"," userResponse":" YANANIPANGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076050808","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076050808"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076051354","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076051354"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076053771","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076053771"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076054655","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076054655"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076055159","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076055158"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076056229","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076056228"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076058700","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076058700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076059696","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076059695"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076062823","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076062823"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076063087","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076063087"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076064062","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076064061"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076066759","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076066759"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076067557","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076067556"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076068754","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076068754"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANASONGA"," userResponse":" YANASONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076069363","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076069363"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076069839","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076069838"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076072190","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076072189"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076073076","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076073075"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076073549","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076073549"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076074566","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076074565"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076077035","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076077035"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076078030","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076078030"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076081408","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076081407"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076082836","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076082835"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076083331","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076083329"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076084062","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076084062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076085108","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076085107"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTETEMEKA"," userResponse":" KUTETEMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076088057","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076088056"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076089416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076089415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAANGUKA"," userResponse":" YANAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076089781","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076089780"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076090369","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076090368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076093256","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076093255"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076094248","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076094247"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076094749","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076094749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076097275","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076097274"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076098271","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076098270"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076101406","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076101405"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076101601","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076101601"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076102337","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076102337"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076103675","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076103675"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUNACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076105001","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076105000"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076105919","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076105918"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076106953","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076106953"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUSIA"," userResponse":" KUNUSIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076108232","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076108231"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076108951","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076108951"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAZO"," userResponse":" AMBAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076109479","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076109479"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076110708","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076110707"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" ANATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076113163","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076113163"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076114062","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076114062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076114576","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076114575"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076115640","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076115639"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076118075","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076118074"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076119070","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076119070"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076122446","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076122446"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILAURI"," userResponse":" BILAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076122951","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076122950"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYO"," userResponse":" ILIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076123932","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076123932"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076125019","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076125019"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAANGUKA"," userResponse":" INAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076125496","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076125496"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076125701","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076125700"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076126526","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076126525"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076129042","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076129041"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASHUKURU"," userResponse":" NASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076129638","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076129638"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUNGU"," userResponse":" MUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076130627","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076130626"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076131275","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076131275"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076133825","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076133825"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076134682","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076134682"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076135449","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076135449"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATILI"," userResponse":" UKATILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076135871","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076135871"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076138292","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076138292"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076138815","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076138814"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076139829","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076139828"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076140103","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076140102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076141003","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076141002"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076144279","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076144278"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIRIMBI"," userResponse":" FIRIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076145436","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076145436"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAPULIZWA"," userResponse":" INAPULIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076147735","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076147734"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076147906","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076147905"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076148534","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076148534"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076149484","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076149484"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAINGIA"," userResponse":" LINAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076152350","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076152350"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SILIONI"," userResponse":" SILIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076153247","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076153246"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076153844","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076153843"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076154215","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076154214"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076154749","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076154749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076157176","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076157176"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076158056","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076158056"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076158531","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076158529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076159548","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076159547"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076162028","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076162027"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076163025","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076163024"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076166908","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076166907"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haionekani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONEKANI"," userResponse":" HAIONEKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076170073","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076170073"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haisikiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAISIKIKI"," userResponse":" HAISIKIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076172696","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076172694"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAFANYA"," userResponse":" INAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076173091","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076173089"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076173699","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076173697"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076174458","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076174457"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076174915","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076174913"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076177489","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076177489"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076177924","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076177923"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076178738","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076178737"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076181214","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076181214"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076181968","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076181967"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076184177","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076184177"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076184933","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076184932"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076189553","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076189553"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076189609","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076189609"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076196284","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076196284"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 9056d5b5-7bd7-4432-b538-3847763e245e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076207535","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076207534"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" RUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076209921","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076209920"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUKA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUKA"," userResponse":" RUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076211559","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076211559"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAMANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076214120","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076214119"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAMANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAMANI"," userResponse":" RAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076215742","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076215741"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" REDIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" REDIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076218686","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076218686"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" REDIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" REDIO"," userResponse":" REDIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076220303","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076220302"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RANGI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076222737","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076222737"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RANGI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076224344","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076224343"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAFIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076227579","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076227579"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAFIKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076229205","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076229204"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" RAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076231573","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076231572"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RAHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAHA"," userResponse":" RAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076233169","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076233169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RINDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076235873","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076235873"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RINDA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076237498","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076237497"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RADHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076239939","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076239939"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RADHI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADHI"," userResponse":" RADHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076241553","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076241553"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076245431","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076245430"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-R.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076247454","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076247453"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076247553","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076247553"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0a66f179-a08b-4e45-b04a-d699fa867160"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-R.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" RUNINGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RUNINGA"," userResponse":" RUNINGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076257275","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076257275"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_4-3-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076262098","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076262098"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_6-0-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076267092","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076267092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_4-8-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076271599","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076271599"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_6-1-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076276193","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076276193"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_6-1-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076281030","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076281030"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-0-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076286178","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076286178"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-3-5"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076290814","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076290814"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076295483","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076295483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_1-2-3"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076300366","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076300366"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-5-0"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076304866","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076304866"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_5-3-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076309552","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076309552"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_5-3-6"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076314257","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076314257"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-7-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076318859","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076318859"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-7-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076325416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076325415"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" ee5bf28d-54b2-443e-af90-e10a598957bd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_5_0-7-5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076334424","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076334423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076334806","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076334805"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076335298","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076335298"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076335650","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076335650"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076336063","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076336062"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076336546","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076336545"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076336778","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076336777"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076340010","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076340010"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076340049","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076340048"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076340771","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076340770"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076341169","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076341169"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076341470","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076341470"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076341683","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076341682"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076341884","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076341883"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076342207","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076342207"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076342439","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076342439"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076345622","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076345622"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076346027","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076346027"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076348542","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076348542"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076348744","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076348744"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076348946","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076348946"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076352441","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076352441"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076356156","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076356156"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076357179","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076357178"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076359895","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076359895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076360267","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076360267"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076360750","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076360749"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076361093","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076361092"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076361495","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076361495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076361969","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076361969"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076362192","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076362192"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076365456","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076365454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076365496","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076365495"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076366209","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076366208"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076366602","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076366602"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076366895","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076366895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076367098","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076367098"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076367291","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076367291"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076367603","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076367603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076367827","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076367827"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076370542","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076370541"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076370637","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076370637"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076425802","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076425800"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 0b86aad7-cdc9-4daf-80ff-661f58da5271"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076425876","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076425876"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" d7216363-fc7f-4247-99f6-12a38ebddb10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:R..R.all.10.rand.say.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076432318","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076432317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" d7216363-fc7f-4247-99f6-12a38ebddb10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.q2s.AV.mc.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076438293","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076438293"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" d7216363-fc7f-4247-99f6-12a38ebddb10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076443505","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076443505"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" d7216363-fc7f-4247-99f6-12a38ebddb10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076450868","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076450867"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" d7216363-fc7f-4247-99f6-12a38ebddb10"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076461492","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076461492"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076463411","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076463410"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076464963","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076464963"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076468757","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076468757"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076470317","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076470317"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076474299","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076474299"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076475893","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076475893"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076478567","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076478566"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076479340","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076479340"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076480127","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076480127"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076488816","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076488816"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076488902","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076488901"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" a4d52218-0dd1-445d-89e7-d972071fb359"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076504260","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076504260"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076504904","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076504903"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076524497","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076524497"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076542895","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076542895"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076552306","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076552306"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076560996","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076560996"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076574129","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076574129"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076583370","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076583370"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076591320","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076591320"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076600008","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076600008"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076608378","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076608378"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076617020","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076617020"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076628198","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076628198"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076639891","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076639890"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076650761","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076650761"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076660603","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076660603"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076664924","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076664924"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076673610","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076673609"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" fcfccad8-3744-422c-94f0-1f454f97785e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076691861","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076691861"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076693120","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076693120"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_112"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076710139","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076710138"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076719546","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076719546"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076729593","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076729593"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076740416","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076740416"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076752721","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076752720"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076763891","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076763891"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076773600","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076773600"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076781997","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076781997"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_7"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076791646","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076791646"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076800846","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076800846"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076809743","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076809743"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076813075","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076813075"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.num.trc:WR-1..10.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076821561","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076821561"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550076828831","data":{"timestamp":" 1550076828831"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077060168","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077060167"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 93b42b17-347c-474e-8e75-fcccb438ca53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.num.trc_WR-1..10.2__it_2"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_10"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077060273","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077060273"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" 3a0eb1c2-79ff-4965-9d7f-f7d948146fa7"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuwepo nyumbani kunako chakaa mradi kwako ni bora kuliko kuwepo nyumbani kuzuri sana angalau ni nyumba ya jirani yako."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077074204","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077074204"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077080980","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077080980"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077087947","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077087947"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077096081","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077096081"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077099423","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077099423"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077102733","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077102733"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077106108","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077106108"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077111368","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077111368"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077115144","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077115144"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077118479","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077118478"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077122102","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077122102"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077125206","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077125206"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077131394","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077131394"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077134413","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077134413"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077139742","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077139742"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077143045","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077143045"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077146854","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077146854"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077150529","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077150529"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1550077153512","data":{"timestamp":" 1550077153512"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190213_193941"," gameId":" f2c72854-5f0b-485c-85f3-2458de3b22ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_17"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}